# **AYLIN DEBRUYNE**

# Full Stack Software Engineer

Atlanta, GA

# Contact

Email: adebruyne88@gmail.com

Phone: 703-674-7777

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/

in/aylindebruyne/

Github: https://github.com/

adebruyne

#### Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express, Handlebars, React, Redux, PostgreSQL, Git, Python

# Education

# **DigitalCrafts**

Summer 2018 // Atlanta, GA 16-week full stack immersive software development program

### **George Mason University**

2006 - 2010 // Fairfax, VA Bachelor of Arts in Psychology, Minor in Fine Arts

# Victoria University of Wellington

Fall 2008 // New Zealand Study Abroad

### Achievements

#### Completed (thru-hiked):

Pacific Crest Trail (2017) Appalachian Trail (2013) Camino de Santiago, Spain (2012)

#### **REI Anderson Award Winner**

(2016)

### Languages

# **Turkish**

Verbal and written fluency

# **Summary**

Outdoor enthusiast turned software engineer. I love taking on new challenges, which is why I entered the exciting field of web development. When I first entered web development, it immediately reminded me of my very first solo backpacking experience; I recognized I had a lot to learn – but I quickly found fulfillment in the creative aspect of coding along with achieving the satisfaction that results from problem-solving.

# **Projects**

#### QuizMe!

June 2016 // https://github.com/adebruyne/flashcard-app

- QuizMe is a flash card app to help new programmers practice their knowledge of the ever-evolving concepts, languages and algorithms of the tech world
- Built with Node.js, Express, Handlebars, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Nginx, AWS

# R.A.D. Hiking

June 2016 // https://github.com/rbrook22/Trail-App

- R.A.D. hiking is an app to help users find the perfect hike based on zip code
- Built with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, The Hiking Project API, Google Geocode API

# **Prior Experience**

### Outdoor School Instructor/ Sales Lead @ REI

Sept. 2014 - July 2017 // Fairfax, VA & Asheville, NC

- Anderson Award Winner (2016)
- Deliver inspirational experiences to customers through effective promotion of outdoor programs

### Front-End Manager @ Epicure Cafe

Jan. 2014 - Nov. 2014 // Fairfax, Va

- Lead and manage staff, communicating daily targets and overseeing responsibility for maintaining high standards of hygiene and quality

### Social Worker @ Cornerstones, Inc.

Nov. 2011 - May 2014 // Reston, Va

- Provide counseling services to homeless, mentally ill, substance abuse-afflicted men and women

#### Customer Service Team Lead @ MOM's Organic Market

July 2011 - Mar. 2013 // Herndon, VA

- Established and maintained superb relationships with all team members and guests while handling special requests and tactfully resolving customer complaints

# Store Manager/Barista @ Caribou Coffee, Inc.

March 2006 - April 2011 // Fairfax, VA

- Established innovative and highly successful weekly music performance night